[
  [
    {
      "question": "What is JavaScript?",
      "answer": "JavaScript is a scripting language used to create and control dynamic website content, i.e. anything that moves, refreshes, or changes on the screen. If HTML were the nouns in a sentence, and CSS were the adjectives, then JavaScript would be the verbs."
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most current version of JavaScript?",
      "answer": "ECMAScript 6 (2015)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the three ways to implement JavaScript?",
      "answer": "Inline (not recommended), Internal (sometimes appropriate), and External (preferred method)."
    },
    {
      "question": "Is white space meaningful in JavaScript?",
      "answer": "In theory, no. In practice, most people will likely keep a well defined style or use a style tool such as the Prettier extension in Visual Studio Code."
    },
    {
      "question": "Is Case Sensitivity important in JavaScript?",
      "answer": "Yes! A variable named 'something' is different than 'Something'."
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the two ways to add comments?",
      "answer": "Single line comments using //, and multi-line comments starting with /* and ending with */ . "
    },
    {
      "question": "Are Semicolons optional in javaScript?",
      "answer": "In most cases, you can omit semicolons altogether. However, under certain circumstances, omitting semicolons can have unexpected results."
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you open the console in a browser?",
      "answer": "Open browser > right click > inspect > console"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you log a message to the console?",
      "answer": "console.log()"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "What are the three Variable Types?",
      "answer": "const(declared values cannot be reassigned, let(declared values can be reassigned), and var(used in previous JavaScript versions, and should be avoided if possible)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the Primitive Types?",
      "answer": "String, Number, and Boolean"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a string?",
      "answer": "A string is anything, such as text, wrapped in single quotes, double quotes, or backticks."
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "3",
      "answer": "3"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "4",
      "answer": "4"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "5",
      "answer": "5"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "6",
      "answer": "6"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "7",
      "answer": "7"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "8",
      "answer": "8"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "9",
      "answer": "9"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "10",
      "answer": "10"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "What is a Regular Expression (RegEx)?",
      "answer": "A regular expression is a sequence of characters that forms a search pattern. Example: /bitwise/i; is a regular expression, while 'bitwise' is the search pattern. 'i' is a modifier which modifies the search to be case-insensitive."
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the two ways to construct a regular expression?",
      "answer": "1. Using a regular expression literal ( const re = /ab+c/; ).<br><br>2. Calling the constructor function of the RegExp object ( const re = new RegExp('ab+c); )."
    },
    {
      "question": "What are JavaScript modules used for?",
      "answer": "JavaScript modules allow you to break up your code into seperate files."
    },
    {
      "question": "Instead of using 'defer', how do you prepare the HTML file for a JavaScript module?",
      "answer": "Use type='module'"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the two ways to export a function or a variable from a file?",
      "answer": "1. In-line individually by including the keyword 'export' before the variable or function ( export const age = 28; ).<br><br>2. All at once by wrapping the variables and functions in curly braces, preceeded by the 'export' keyword ( export {name, age, height}; ). "
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the two ways to import modules into a file?",
      "answer": "1. Import from named exports ( import { name, age } from './person.js'; ).<br><br>2. Import from default exports ( import message from './message.js' )."
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "What is an IIFE (Immediately Invoked Function Expression)?",
      "answer": "It is a JavaScript function that runs as soon as it it defined. It is also known as a Self-Executing Anonymous Function."
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the two major parts of an IIFE?",
      "answer": "1. The first is the anonymous function with lexical scope enclosed within the Grouping Operator (). This prevents accessing variables within the IIFE idiom as well as polluting the global scope.<br><br>2. The second part creates the immediately invoked function expression () through which the JavaScript engine will directly interpret the function"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you create an ES6 Block Scope?",
      "answer": "By wrapping const and let variables within curly brackets. These can be easier to use than an IIFE (Immediately Invoked Function Expression)."
    }
  ]
]
